Speaker: PART 3
Some months later, Mrs Myers appeared in court.
ÔSo, Mrs Myers,Ő said the judge, ÔwhatŐs all this with the cards?Ő
ÔI need to earn money,Ő said the old lady.
ÔAt my age, IŐm not going to be a dancer!Ő
ÔSomebody complained that you are not reading the cards properly,Ő said the judge.
ÔIf theyŐre going to pay you a pound, people expect a proper reading.Ő
ÔBut most people donŐt complain,Ő the old lady replied.
ÔI tell them things they want to hear. And sometimes I even get it rightÉŐ
ÔBut,Ő said the judge, Ôhere we have a witness.
Please tell us about it, Mrs McCleary.Ő
ÔMrs Myers read the cards for me,Ő said Mrs McCleary.
ÔShe told me that in a year IŐd be married, that my husband would be
a rich young man and that weŐd move abroad.Ő
ÔBut Mrs McCleary is already married,Ő said the judge.
ÔShe married Inspector McCleary three years ago.
So how do you explain this nonsense, Mrs Myers?Ő
ÔWell, she said she was single,Ő said the old lady, calmly.
ÔSo I predicted a wedding for her and a rich husband.Ő
ÔAnd what about the old man and the journey abroad?Ő asked Mrs McCleary.
ÔFor something more to say,Ő replied Mrs Myers.
ÔFor a pound you need to say more than just two things.Ő
ÔYou are a fraud, Mrs Myers,Ő said the judge.
ÔYou must pay a fine of fifty pounds.
I hope you learn your lesson.Ő